# NERMIN MEMOVIC

### WEB DEVELOPER



+38166100751



nermin.memovic990@gmail.com



Linkedin

# SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- JS / jQuery
- Wordpress
- ACF Plugin
- CPT
- Ajax
- GSAP
- Figma
- SEO
- Boostrap 5
- Git

# EDUCATION

# FTN, KOSOVSKA MITROVICA - MASTER'S DEGREE

Environmental engineering

2017 - 2020

## FTN, KOSOVSKA MITROVICA -BACHELOR'S DEGREE

Environmental engineering

2009 - 2017

# **PROFILE**

I'm a Web Developer with three years of experience. I specialize in creating websites in WordPress, developing custom themes, using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP. I mainly focus on front-end development, and I plan to further improve my skills by learning React. I work well in teams but am also prepared for independent work.

# EXPERIENCE

#### **BUREAU TWENTYTWO**

Web Developer

2021 - present

#### PROFESSOR OF NATURAL SCIENCE

Technical School, Kosovska Mitrovica 2018 - 2021

# **PROJECTS**

All project below designed and dev by Bureau Twentytwo

### <u>3AP</u>

Frontend & backend

### THE DAILY MUCK

Frontend & backend

### **BUREAU TWENTYTWO**

Frontend & backend

#### **PLANT BY NUMBER**

Frontend

#### **LUCHA T8**

Frontend

## **EXECUTIVE ASSISTANCE**

Frontend

### **SEAWALL POINT**

Frontend